<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- Fleshling -->

  <GR_Fleshling.label>fleshling</GR_Fleshling.label>
  <GR_Fleshling.description>Something went terribly wrong. This wretched creature is struggling to keep breathing. Whilst it doesn’t pose any real threat and it seems quite friendly, it requires a tremendous amount of love and attention for it to find the strength to live another day.</GR_Fleshling.description>
  <GR_Fleshling.tools.0.label>bite</GR_Fleshling.tools.0.label>


  <!-- Aberrant Fleshbeast -->

  <GR_AberrantFleshbeast.label>aberrant fleshbeast</GR_AberrantFleshbeast.label>
  <GR_AberrantFleshbeast.description>Something went terribly wrong. This wretched creature is struggling to keep breathing. Whilst it doesn’t pose any threat and will slowly bleed to death, attacking it can trigger its self-defense instincts.</GR_AberrantFleshbeast.description>
  <GR_AberrantFleshbeast.tools.0.label>bite</GR_AberrantFleshbeast.tools.0.label>


  <!-- Flesh Monstrosity -->

  <GR_FleshMonstrosity.label>flesh monstrosity</GR_FleshMonstrosity.label>
  <GR_FleshMonstrosity.description>Something went terribly wrong. This wretched creature is struggling to keep breathing. It’s rabid, and the moment it crawled out of the vat it started to look for the next unfortunate living being to destroy. It can and should be slain as soon as possible, as each additional kill only prolongs its life.</GR_FleshMonstrosity.description>
  <GR_FleshMonstrosity.tools.0.label>bite</GR_FleshMonstrosity.tools.0.label>


  <!-- Flesh Growth -->

  <GR_FleshGrowth.label>flesh growth</GR_FleshGrowth.label>
  <GR_FleshGrowth.description>Something went terribly wrong. A huge and weird growth has spawned within the electrowomb, breaking it completely and spreading all around. This growth is a hatchery for small flies that can devour any living creature to the bone. It seems to be sensitive to daylight, but no one knows how far it can spread at night.</GR_FleshGrowth.description>
  <GR_FleshGrowth.tools.0.label>bite</GR_FleshGrowth.tools.0.label>


  <!-- Flesh Flies -->

  <GR_FleshFlies.label>flesh flies</GR_FleshFlies.label>
  <GR_FleshFlies.description>A swarm of small, deadly flies. Almost impossible to hit using rudimentary weapons, the ideal way of dealing with fleshflies is by using fire, to which they are highly susceptible.</GR_FleshFlies.description>
  <GR_FleshFlies.tools.0.label>bite</GR_FleshFlies.tools.0.label>


</LanguageData>